hollisterco.com 2017-02-17

# Customer Service | HollisterCo.com

## Hollister Co. US  
Privacy Policy

Updated: February 2017

## Ad Cookie Policy

## How Third Parties Serve You Our Advertisements On Other Websites and Your Choices

Hollister Co. (also referred to in this policy and the privacy policy below as "we," "us," "our," or"HCo") contracts with third party advertising companies to serve you online display and banner advertisements on other Websites.  To serve this advertising, these third parties may place, use or rely on technology, such as cookies and/or Pixel Tags (which are described below in the privacy policy), to collect information about your interactions with our Websites and Apps (both defined below in the privacy policy) and interactions with other websites. These advertising companies may use and share the information gathered to deliver our ads more tailored to your interests on other websites that are a part of their online advertising networks and/or search engines.  We receive aggregate information from these third parties to gauge our advertising effectiveness.

For information about opt out programs these third party advertising companies participate in and the effect of opting out, click on the following: <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/> and <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/> (you will leave this Website for a separately managed online site where you can specify your preference under those programs).  You can also click on the icon that may appear on some of our advertising served through these technologies.  We may use more than one third party company for placing this advertising, which would require you to opt out of each company.

## Privacy Policy

This privacy policy statement applies only to the information collected: online through HollisterCo.com, Hollister Co. microsites or mobile sites (collectively our “Websites”), our emails, our text messages, or mobile applications Hollister Co. provided for download to your mobile device (“Apps”) that expressly adopt and display or link to this privacy policy; or through our pages on social media sites, such as Facebook, Twitter, et al. (“Social Media Pages").

In order to make your visits to the various channels of Hollister Co. as responsive as possible, we collect information when you visit us online. To help ensure an enjoyable online experience, we provide this summary of what information we collect online, and how that information is used. Your use of the Website/App confirms your acceptance of this privacy policy and your agreement to be bound by it. If you do not accept this privacy policy, do not use this Website/App.

## Contents

## Information Collected Online

### 1\. General Browsing

We collect general information about our visitors’ experience with our Websites and this general information is not connected to personally identifiable information about individual visitors. The information collected includes which pages our visitors are viewing on our Websites and whether visitors arrived through a link for our Websites.  It also includes information on the type of browser and service provider used.  For visitors using a mobile version of our Websites, this includes technical information about the device used, such as screen size, cookie support by the device and how images may appear.   All of this information helps us provide a better experience for our visitors by being able to determine such things as how to best format our mobile Websites for various devices, our most desired pages, products and features, how to best direct visitors to our Websites, and where there might be browser or service provider connection issues.

### 2\. Location Information 

Our Websites and emails may include features that require collecting different types of location information as described below:

  * Websites: Features include things such as check-in, find in store, or find a product in stores. We may use various technologies to determine location, such as location services included in your browser or your device, IP Address, and sensor data locating your device near Wi-Fi access points, Bluetooth devices or beacons, and cell towers. Some of these technologies may require enabling location-based services and/or your consent for our Websites to access your location information.
  * Emails: Our emails may use your IP address to determine the city in which you are located when you open the email.  This allows us to tailor content to you, such as a map of nearby stores.

Mobile devices referenced above include your cell phone, and could include your laptop or tablet depending on the type of wireless connectivity used. If you do not consent to provide or disable location-based services, we may ask you to manually select the region where you are located, or to enter your zip code; if you chose not to provide this information some features of the Websites may not be available.  See the “Opt-Out” section below for the choices you have regarding collection of location information.

### 3\. Personally Identifiable Information We Collect

Hollister Co. collects personally identifiable information from you when you provide us with this information, either by filling out all or a portion of a form, or completing the form by submitting it. You can provide us this personally identifiable information in many instances throughout our Websites, or by sending us an email or a text message, for example when you interact with the following opportunities: placing an order through one of our Websites; establishing an account, joining, participating or becoming a member in the Club Cali program (collectively “Membership”); adding your choices and information about yourself and others to your Membership; submitting content to our Websites, Apps or Social Media Pages, such as comments, product reviews, pictures or videos; registering to participate in a promotion; emailing an item, post card or wish list; adding a message in the gift wrap section or on an E-Gift Card; entering a contest or sweepstakes; requesting an opportunity to model for us; taking a survey; contacting us with a comment or question; signing up to receive emails or text messages about our products and services; replying to an email or text message requesting information from you; requesting to receive investor alerts; or applying for a job online. We also collect information through use of cookies, pixel tags (also known as Web beacons and clear GIFs), and URL links, as described under "Cookies" below. While not personally identifiable information by itself, Hollister Co. also collects and retains the following information and associates it with your personally identifiable information: your IP address, your interactions with the Websites, your actions in response to our communications to you, and the purchases you make.

Categories of personally identifiable information collected online include name, address, gender, month and day of birth, email address, telephone number, mobile phone number, payment card information, recipient's name, address and email address, modeling information (including name, size stats, work information, and contact information), use of our Websites tied to one of these categories and any other information you choose to provide, including through your personal social media accounts, as described below.

### 4\. Personal Information You Allow Us to Collect from Your Social Media Accounts

To create an account on our Websites or to participate in certain features, our Websites may allow you to choose to let us access information from accounts you have created on social media sites such as Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest, Instagram, and other similar sites (“Personal Social Media Accounts”). If you chose to allow us access to your Personal Social Media Accounts, Hollister Co. could collect some, and possible all, of the data in the Personal Social Media Account to which you grant access.  Depending on the terms of the social media site, this information could include: your name, email address, profile picture, gender, networks, user ID, list of friends, birthday, likes, education history, work history, current city, hometown, interests, relationship status, and location.  Once you grant this permission, Hollister Co. will be able to continue to be linked to the permitted Personal Social Media Account and collect information without a further request for permission, which could include later revisions to existing information or new types of information that you add.  If you no longer want your Personal Social Media Account(s) linked to our Websites, click on the ‘disconnect’ link located on your account profile page, and we will stop collecting this information.  You may also be able to stop our ability to link to information in your Personal Social Media Account by following instructions provided on the applicable social media sites.

This privacy policy does not cover the privacy and security practices of social media sites where you have Personal Social Media Accounts. Please review privacy policies and terms of service on the social media sites if you have any questions about their privacy or security practices.

## Mobile Application

We offer Apps for download to your mobile device that provide you with various interactive features.

The collection and means of collecting information through any currently existing or future App are discussed in this policy when referencing Websites under the following sections:

  * "General Browsing"
  * "Location Information"
  * "Personally Identifiable Information We Collect"
  * "Personal Information You Allow Us to Collect from Your Social Media Accounts"
  * "Cookies"

The use and sharing of information through any currently existing or future App are discussed in this policy when referencing Websites under the following sections:

  * "Using Information We Collect Online"
  * "Information We Share With Third Parties"
  * "Cookies"

In addition:

  * Use of some features of an App will ask for permission to access data on your mobile device, such as your photos. We will only access this data if you provide consent when asked by the App. Please note, some features of the App are only available if you allow us to access the requested content.
  * If you provide consent when asked, the App will send push notifications ("Notifications") to your mobile device. These Notifications can be sent to you and viewed by you even if you are not actively using the App.  The Notifications may be specific to your interactions with us and may be location-specific if you have consented to location-based services. 
  * Information about preventing the collection of location-based information through the App is provided when referencing Websites under the "Mobile Device Location Information" subsection of "Opt-Out" below.
  * See the “Opt-Out” section below for the choices you have regarding collection of data from your mobile device, and receipt of Notifications.

Personal information may be collected directly by Hollister Co. through our Social Media Pages and may also be collected by the social media site hosting the Hollister Co. Social Media Page.

Personal Information collected directly by Hollister Co.: The collection of personal information directly by Hollister Co. on our Social Media Pages will include the type of information addressed under "Personally Identifiable Information We Collect" above. Examples of how personal information may be directly collected on Hollister Co. Social Media Pages include providing information through an application or form which has a link to this privacy policy. We will use and share the information we collect on our Social Media Pages in the manner specified below in "Using Information We Collect Online" and in "Information We Share With Third Parties."

Personal Information collected by the social media sites: This privacy policy does not cover the privacy and security practices of the social media sites on which Hollister Co. has Social Media Pages. Please review privacy policies and terms of service on the social media sites if you have any questions about their privacy or security practices.

The social media sites where Hollister Co. has Social Media Pages may provide aggregate information and analysis to Hollister Co. about your use of our Social Media Pages. This allows us to better understand and analyze our user growth, general demographic information about the users of our Social Media Pages, and interaction with content on our Social Media Pages. Overall, this information may be used to help us understand the types of visitors and users of our Social Media Pages and use of the content.

## Using Information We Collect Online

We may use the information we collect under this policy (including information collected through cookies; see below section on “Cookies” and "How Third Parties Serve You Our Advertisements On Other Websites and Your Choices" noted above for details on cookies and how we use them), to fulfill product orders; to fulfill your requests (such as contact us, click to chat, email a friend, coming soon product alert, wish list, shipping updates, or a post card); to contact you or the product recipient(s) in the event of order or delivery difficulties; to serve site content; to provide marketing communications regarding our products, services and promotions to you (including sending cart abandonment emails) and to people in your Membership address book; to administer our Hollister Club Cali program; to post content you provide to us through our Websites, Apps or Social Media Pages, such as comments, reviews or images on our Websites, Apps and Social Media Pages, or use it in our marketing communications; to analyze your activity with us, including interaction with our Websites/emails/text messages, the effectiveness of our advertising and your purchases; to personalize our communications to you; to respond to your inquiries and other communications; to update information maintained in your online Membership; to conduct surveys, sweepstakes or contests; to develop our products, services, and Websites; and to consider you for employment. Hollister Co. uses the information collected on its Social Media Pages to send communications regarding our products, services, and promotions; to respond to your inquiries; to conduct surveys, sweepstakes or contests; to analyze your activity on our Social Media Pages and to develop our products and services.  See the “Opt-Out” section below for the choices you have related to receiving marketing communications from us.

We may use the information that we collect under this Privacy Policy for the purpose of providing personalized content across different Internet browsers or devices that you use to access our Websites and mobile applications, including the synchronization of wish lists and shopping bags. Any changes made to privacy settings (including your opt-out preferences) on one browser or device will not be synchronized between browsers and/or devices. Alternatively, any changes made to privacy settings must be made on each browser or device on an individual basis.

If you previously signed up for the original Club Cali, even though the program no longer exists, HollisterCo.com has retained your name, email address, and postal address for marketing purposes.

_We may disclose the information that you provide to us (including, without limitation, your personal data) to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company, and the subsidiaries of our holding company (including our affiliated companies)._ **HCo and its affiliated companies will not subscribe you to their ongoing marketing email and/or text message programs unless you have separately consented to receive such marketing communications from a given affiliated company.**

We make the names and postal addresses in our postal mailing list, sometimes categorized by purchasing information, available to other unaffiliated companies for their marketing purposes.  See the “Opt-Out” section below for instructions on how to opt out of sharing with unaffiliated companies.

If you submit content to us through our Websites, Apps or Social Media Pages, such as comments, reviews or images, and we choose to post your content on our Websites or otherwise display it, it will become public information.  

Please be aware that we may use third parties to assist us with our e-commerce business, such as our Websites, emails, text messages, and Social Media Pages. Some examples of the assistance that may be provided by third party service providers are: fulfilling orders (including, but not limited to, processing payments, providing fraud prevention services, and verifying addresses); providing advertising services, including on social media sites and internet search engines; monitoring and analyzing site activity, your actions in response to emails and the effectiveness of our advertising; providing support services; facilitating communication with you through emails, texts, Notifications, and other platforms; conducting surveys; administering and maintaining employment application information; offering interactive features; and administering our Hollister Club Cali program, product reviews, promotions, sweepstakes or contests. Personal information you provide us may be shared, as necessary, with the relevant third parties to so carry out functions on our behalf. It is possible that some of these service providers will be located outside of the United States.

You should also be aware that we may disclose specific information about you if necessary to do so by law or based on our good faith belief that it is necessary to conform or comply with the law or is necessary to protect the users of our Websites, the Websites or the public.

If HollisterCo.com were ever merged with or it or its assets were acquired by another company, or if it acquires another business entity or is involved in a corporate reorganization or other change of control, some or all of the personal information collected about you could be shared with this entity, and may also be retained by HollisterCo.com. Other than this acquisition, sale or reorganization, we do not sell or rent your email address to unrelated third parties.

## Cookies

### What Are Cookies, Pixel Tags and URL Links, and How Are These Used on Our Websites or in Our Emails?

Our Websites and email use, and our third party service providers may use, a browser feature known as a cookie, which assigns a unique identification to your computer or device. The cookies are typically stored on your computer's hard drive or mobile device. The information collected when visiting our Websites or interacting with our emails may include the following: an IP address; the URL of the page from which you arrived; your browser type; other technical information about your device used to visit our Websites or interact with our emails; the pages you view; the features you use; whether you sign up for Membership, or sign in and where you go on our Websites once signed into your Membership; whether you complete a transaction; whether you have previously completed a survey; and the time of your visit. This information allows us to determine such things as which parts of our Websites are most visited or used, what products are browsed and/or purchased, the effectiveness of our Websites and emails, your specific interaction with our Websites and emails, and difficulties you may experience in accessing our Websites or our emails. With this knowledge, we can improve the quality of your experience on our Websites  and interaction with our emails by recognizing and delivering more of the most desired features and information, personalize your experience, and resolve access difficulties. In addition, our Websites use cookies to help keep track of items you put into your shopping cart or wish list, whether you purchase any or all of those items, and to tell us whether you have visited one of our Websites in the past. This allows you to maintain shopping carts and wish lists between visits, and allows us to inquire about your continued interest in items in your shopping cart or wish list or that you viewed on one of our Websites. Our Websites also use cookies to help keep track of checkout information, other than payment method information, while you remain on our site. In addition, the information collected by us or our service provider(s) may be linked to and combined with information that we collect about you from your visits to our Websites or interaction with our emails.

Our Websites and emails use, and our third party service providers may also use, Pixel Tags (also known as Web beacons, Web bugs, and Clear GIFs). A Pixel Tag is a nearly invisible pixel-sized graphic image on a Webpage or email message. Pixel Tags may be used to collect the same information about your visit that is collected through cookies, as noted above. We may also collect information about a search engine used, and a search engine advertisement clicked to navigate to the Websites. Pixel Tags in emails also help us confirm the receipt of, and response to, our emails (including your interaction with your Websites as a result of receiving the email) and the time our email is viewed. This information helps us to make similar evaluations about our Websites and emails as with cookies and to determine the most desired features and information so that we can provide those features and information to you and personalize our interactions with you. This information may also be linked to and combined with information that we collect about you from your visits to our Websites.

In addition, our communications (e.g. emails, text messages, direct messages via social media platforms, et al.) to you may include "click-through URLs" linked to particular pages on one of our Websites. By clicking on one of the URLs, you will automatically enter one of our Websites. Through the use of cookies, we may associate identifying information in the click-through URL with your previous experiences on our Websites. You may avoid having this information collected by not clicking on the URL links in our communications.

## Opt-Out

To make it easier for you, we have moved your opt-out preference choices to this section of the privacy policy.

### Collection of Location Information:

  * Mobile Device Location Information Through Our Mobile Websites:Your mobile device may allow you to disable location-based services on your device, which will prevent our Websites from accessing your mobile device location information. For specific questions regarding disabling your device's location services, we recommend that you review the specific instructions provided for your mobile device. Note that some features on our Websites, such as check-in, may not be available if you disable location-based services.
  * Desktop Device Location Information Through Website Features:Your desktop web browser may allow you to remove the permission you granted through your desktop device for our Websites to access your location information and/or completely block requests for location information. For specific questions regarding disabling your web browser's location services, we recommend that you review the specific instructions provided with your web browser.
  * Location Information Through Emails:Your email program may allow you to prevent the images in the emails you receive from us from downloading, which will also prevent our service provider from accessing your location information. You can also unsubscribe from receiving our emails, as described in the "Email" section below.

### Notifications and Access to Data on Your Mobile Device:

If you have provided consent and no longer wish to receive Notifications, or no longer want us to access the specific information on your device (e.g., photos, etc) for which you previously gave consent, you will need to adjust the settings on your mobile device. Please note, the process for changing settings on your mobile device may vary; to learn how to change these settings refer to the specific instructions provided for your mobile device.

### Emails:

To unsubscribe from receiving marketing emails Hollister Co. go to the [unsubscribe](http://www.hollisterco.com/webapp/wcs/stores/servlet/Unsubscription?storeId=10251&catalogId=10201&langId=-1) page, or if you created an account or are a member of the Club Cali program, go to the Marketing Preferences section of the Profile page. If you signed up to receive marketing emails from one of our affiliates follow the-opt out instructions on any marketing email you receive from that affiliate. Please be aware, however, even if you request to be removed from our email marketing list, you may still receive non-marketing emails, such as confirmations for any orders placed on our Websites.

### Text Messages:

  * Marketing Text Messages:If you have signed up to receive text messages from Hollister Co., or any of our affiliated companies (for example, Abercrombie & Fitch and abercrombie kids), but no longer wish to receive these messages, simply follow the opt-out instructions in the Texts Terms for each brand , i.e. send or reply “STOP” to any text message you have received.  Or, if you created an account or are a member of the Club Cali program, go to the email and phone page within the "My Info" section of the Websites, click on "manage your marketing preferences", and select the option to no longer receive text messages in the drop-down menu for each brand and press ‘SUBMIT.' Please note, if you unsubscribe by sending a text or by going to the email  and phone page within the "My Info" section of the Websites you may receive a reply message confirming that you have opted out of receiving text messages.
  * Shipping Alert Text Messages:If you opted to receive shipping alerts via text message but you no longer wish to receive them, reply STOP to any shipping alert text message you have received.

### Postal Marketing:

If you no longer wish to receive other marketing materials from Hollister Co. via regular postal mail, please click [Privacy_Policy@HollisterCo.com](mailto:privacy_policy@HollisterCo.com) and tell us to remove you from our postal mailing list and include the postal address you wish to have removed.

### Third-Party Postal Address Sharing:

If you would like to make sure that we do not disclose your name and postal address to unaffiliated third parties for their direct marketing purposes, then please email us at [Privacy_Policy@HollisterCo.com ](mailto:privacy_policy@HollisterCo.com)and tell us that you do not want your personal address shared with unaffiliated third parties, including the postal address.

### Facebook Messenger Communication:

You may opt in to receive communication and updates from us about your order via Facebook Messenger. Once consent is provided during checkout on our site, it will be maintained for all future orders. To opt out, open the conversation on Facebook Messenger and click on the “Turn Off” link (located next to the Facebook Messenger updates language). If you elect to delete your HCo account, then you will no longer receive updates via Facebook Messenger.

## If you Apply for a Job or Attend Casting Calls

If you want to work for us, you can submit a curriculum vitae or resume online or fill out an employment application online. When you fill in an online employment application, we will collect personal data such as your name and contact details. We will use this information to evaluate you as a candidate for the position that you applied for and to contact you about the position.

We invite our employees who are interested in becoming a model to attend casting calls. If you would like to attend one of our casting calls, we may ask you to electronically send us information such as your statistics and age and to provide us with photographs or video footage of you. We may share this information and media with the modeling agency that we engage to assist us in determining whether we are interested in you becoming a model.

If you electronically send us information about your interest in being a model for us (such as your name, size stats, work information, contact information, photographs, and video), we will only use that information to determine whether we are interested in you being a model and to contact you about prospective modeling. We may share also that information with our modeling agency. The modeling agency will use your information solely to assist us in determining whether we are interested in you being an Abercrombie & Fitch model.

## International Users

If you are visiting one of our Websites from a location outside of the United States, please keep in mind that it is a US based web and/or commerce site. This privacy policy governs the information collected by or on behalf of our Websites irrespective of where you are located when you access it, browse it, interact with it, and make purchases through it (including those that are shipped to addresses outside the US). If, for any reason, you are accessing a country specific website for a country in which you are not located (e.g. utilizing a proxy server) please contact Customer Service to view the policies and terms specific to your jurisdiction.

With respect to personal information you provide to Hollister Co. on the Social Media Pages, once received from the social media sites, it is maintained and processed by us on servers and internal systems located in the United States. This means your personal information may be stored outside of the province, state, and/or country in which you reside, and processed by us, an affiliate or a third party service provider as described in this privacy policy. Moreover, governmental bodies that have jurisdiction over us in the United States (e.g., courts and law enforcement agencies) may be entitled to access your personal information.

## Updating Personal Information in Your Account

If you have signed up for a Membership we prefer to keep your personal information accurate and up-to-date. To do this, we provide you with the opportunity to update or modify your personal information, including your billing address, preferred shipping information, payment details, and contact information. Just sign in to your Membership with your email address and password, and you'll see an overview page where you can update your information.

To request to have your account cancelled send an email to [Privacy_Policy@HollisterCo.com](mailto:privacy_policy@HollisterCo.com) and include the email address of the account you wish to cancel.

## Privacy of Children

Our Websites that link to this privacy policy are not directed at anyone under the age of 13, and no one under the age of 13 should provide personal information on these Websites.

## Links

For your convenience and enjoyment, our Websites may contain links to other websites. We do not evaluate and are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We would urge you to review the privacy policies on each link to ensure that you are comfortable with their privacy policies and practices.

## Updates to Privacy Policy

As we continue to offer you new and different types of content and services, we may modify our information collection, use or disclosure practices. Should there be a material change to our information collection, use or disclosure practices, it will be applied only to information collected on a going forward basis, and we will update this privacy policy statement.

## Security Statement

Hollister Co. limits the number of employees that have access to the databases that contain personal data, and Hollister Co. employees are advised of the importance of confidentiality. In addition, it is our policy to never send your payment card number via email.

In addition, we designed our online store to accept orders only from Web browsers that permit communication through Transport Layer Security (TLS) technology. Browsers that do not meet this requirement will be prevented from navigating the online store section of our Websites. See "Supported Web Browsers" for more information. While we implement the above security measures on this site, you should be aware that 100% security is not always possible.

## Supported Web Browsers

HollisterCo.com supports Microsoft Internet Explorer 11.0+, Android 4.4+, Apple OS X 10.9+, and Apple iOS 8+.  We recommend if you are viewing our websites on Google Chrome or Mozilla Firefox to download the latest version in order to maximize your experience, otherwise you may not be able to access or utilize all pages on our websites as intended.  

## Questions/Contact Us

If you have any questions, comments or concerns regarding our privacy practices, please email us at [Privacy_Policy@HollisterCo.com](mailto:privacy_policy@HollisterCo.com) or contact us at:

Attn: Privacy Policy Manager  
Abercrombie & Fitch Stores, Inc.  
6301 Fitch Path  
New Albany, Ohio 43054 USA
